<schemalist>
  <schema path="/com/canonical/unity-2d/" id="com.canonical.Unity2d" gettext-domain="unity-2d">
    <key type="b" name="use-opengl">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Use OpenGL viewport.</summary>
      <description>
        Whether to render the graphics into an OpenGL viewport.
        When set to false, the raster engine is used.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key type="s" name="form-factor">
      <default>"desktop"</default>
      <summary>What sort of device Unity is running on.</summary>
      <description>
        Unity will adapt its shape and form to the device it is running on.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key type="b" name="sticky-edges">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Sticky edges.</summary>
      <description>Whether the edges in a multi-monitor setup should be sticky or not (Edges with autohide launchers are always sticky).</description>
    </key>
    <key type="s" name="average-bg-color">
      <default>'#75507B'</default>
      <summary>Average background color</summary>
      <description>The average color derived from the currently set desktop-wallpaper.</description>
    </key>
  </schema>
  <schema path="/com/canonical/unity-2d/launcher/" id="com.canonical.Unity2d.Launcher" gettext-domain="unity-2d">
    <key type="b" name="super-key-enable">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Super key activation.</summary>
      <description>Whether or not the super (also called windows key) key is used.</description>
    </key>
    <key name="hide-mode" type="i">
      <default>0</default>
      <summary>Hiding mode of the launcher</summary>
      <description>Possible values:
        0: never hide; the launcher is always visible and windows won't overlap with it
        1: auto hide; the launcher will disappear after a short time if the user is not interacting with it
        2: intellihide; same as auto hide but the launcher will disappear if a window is placed on top of it
       </description>
    </key>
    <key type="i" name="reveal-mode">
      <default>0</default>
      <summary>Reveal mode</summary>
      <description>Possible values:
        0: Reveal the launcher by pushing the mouse against the left side of the screen (right in RTL)
        1: Reveal the launcher by pushing the mouse against the top-left corner of the screen (top-right in RTL)
       </description>
    </key>
    <key name="edge-responsiveness" type="d">
      <default>2</default>
      <summary>Responsiveness of the Launcher</summary>
      <description>How quickly the Launcher will reveal when you push the pointer against the 
        monitor edge
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="edge-decayrate" type="i">
      <default>1500</default>
      <summary>Decay rate of mouse pressure against barrier</summary>
      <description>The pressures against the monitor edge are continually added up, and when the sum
        hits a certain threshold the launcher reveals. To prevent a series of distinct gentle pushes  
        of the pointer against the barrier from causing the launcher to reveal, we substract this  
        parameter - the decay rate - at a steady rate
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="edge-reveal-pressure" type="i">
      <default>2000</default>
      <summary>Launcher reveal edge pressure</summary>
      <description>The minimum pressure to press the pointer against the monitor edge to 
        cause the launcher to reveal
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="edge-stop-velocity" type="i">
      <default>6500</default>
      <summary>Barrier edge stop velocity</summary>
      <description>The minimum velocity the pointer needs to travel to pass through the barrier without 
        any resistance. Only relevant for multi-monitor setups
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="edge-overcome-pressure" type="i">
      <default>2000</default>
      <summary>Barrier edge overcome pressure
      </summary>
      <description>Minimum pressure the pointer needs to exert on the barrier for the barrier to drop.
        Only relevant for multi-monitor setups
      </description>
    </key>
    <key type="b" name="only-one-launcher">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Show only one launcher.</summary>
      <description>Whether in a multi-monitor setup there should be just one launcher in the primary screen or one in each.</description>
    </key>
  </schema>
  <schema path="/com/canonical/unity-2d/panel/" id="com.canonical.Unity2d.Panel" gettext-domain="unity-2d">
    <key type="as" name="applets">
      <default>["appname", "!legacytray", "indicator"]</default>
      <summary>Applets to display in the panel</summary>
      <description>
        List of panel applets that should be displayed, in order, in the panel.
        Each applet name can be annotated with the prefix "!" to force that applet to be displayed
        only on the panel living in the leftmost screen.
      </description>
    </key>
  </schema>
  <schema path="/com/canonical/unity-2d/dash/" id="com.canonical.Unity2d.Dash" gettext-domain="unity-2d">
    <key type="b" name="full-screen">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>The current fullscreen status of the dash</summary>
      <description>
        Describe if the dash should be fullscreen or not. If the dash is already running this setting
        is applied immediately, otherwise it is applied as soon as the dash is activated again.
      </description>
    </key>
  </schema>
</schemalist>
